[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
This is Granddad Dog's garage.
[HONKS]
Here are Peppa and her family
in their car.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Danny.
[BARKS]
Hello, Peppa.
What can we do for you today?
We've got petrol,
air for tires
and a new
automatic car wash.
Uh, two ice lollies please.
Oh. Certainly.
Granddad Dog's garage
sells lots of things,
even ice lollies.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Thank you. Goodbye.
BOTH: Goodbye.
[HORN HONKS]
[♪♪]
I love our car.
[LAUGHS]
And our car loves us too.
Don't you?
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
Oh, dear.
The car has stopped.
[ENGINE STALLING]
It's no good.
It won't start.
I know.
I'll ring Granddad Dog.
[DIALING]
[RINGING]
Granddad Dog speaking.
Help.
Our car has broken down.
Danny, we've got
some rescuing to do.
Yippee!
[BARKS]
To the rescue!
[HORN HONKS]
[SNORTS]
Look, there's Danny
and Granddad Dog.
ALL:
Hooray!
Granddad Dog knows everything
about cars.
Hmm.
Is it serious?
No. You've just run out
of petrol.
What can we do?
There's plenty of petrol
at my garage.
I'll tow you there.
Granddad Dog is towing
Peppa's car
back to his garage.
[HORN HONKS]
[♪♪]
Granddad Dog is filling
Peppa's car with petrol.
Thank you, Granddad Dog.
[HORN HONKS]
Here are Suzy Sheep
and her mommy in their car.
[BLEATS]
Hello, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Suzy.
We ran out of petrol.
Granddad Dog rescued us.
Wow! That's exciting.
See you later.
[GIGGLING]
[TIRE POPS]
[AIR HISSES]
Oh, no.
All the air has gone out
of the tire.
Will Granddad Dog
have to rescue us?
I think so.
[RINGING]
Granddad Dog speaking.
I see.
Don't panic,
Mommy Sheep,
I'm on my way.
To the rescue!
Can I go too?
Hop aboard, Peppa.
To the rescue!
[GIGGLING]
[HORN HONKS]
Hello, Suzy.
We've come to rescue you.
BOTH:
Hooray!
[♪♪]
Granddad Dog
is filling the tire with air.
[AIR HISSING]
Thank you, Granddad Dog.
[HORN HONKS]
Here are Granny Pig
and Grandpa Pig in their car.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
Would you like
some petrol or air?
No, thanks. I want
to try out your new carwash.
Certainly.
It's run by a computer.
[BEEPS]
COMPUTER:
Hello. I am the carwash
of the future.
ALL:
Ooh!
First, soapy water.
Then a rinse.
And finally, a polish.
ALL:
Wow!
Sorry, I have malfunctioned.
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
The computer has broken.
And Grandpa Pig's car
is stuck.
Aah! Do something,
Granddad Dog!
Oh. I don't know
how to mend computers.
My daddy mended our computer
at home.
Uh, well, I didn't really
mend the computer, I just...
Good. Then this is a job
for Daddy Pig.
Hmm.
Maybe if I just
switch if off.
And then switch it on again.
Daddy Pig has mended
the car wash.
ALL:
Hooray!
Granddad Dog is the best
at mending cars.
But my daddy
mended the carwash.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are going to the playground
today.
Should we drive
to the playground?
No, let's walk.
Look. It's just over there.
The playground
is quite close.
[♪♪]
[LAUGHS]
Okay, let's walk.
[SNORTS]
This way, everyone.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
We're going to the playground.
Oh. Where has the sky gone?
[SNORTS]
Don't worry, Peppa.
It's just fog.
[SNORTS]
What's fog?
Fog is a cloud
that is on the ground
instead of in the sky.
BOTH:
Ooh.
Hmm, it's very thick fog.
PEPPA:
I can't see a thing.
Hmm. Maybe we should
go back home.
Yes, we'll go to the playground
another day.
BOTH:
Oh.
It is too foggy
to find the playground,
so Peppa and George
have to go back home.
Now, which way is home?
[SNORTS]
Are we lost, Daddy Pig?
[LAUGHS]
Don't worry,
I know exactly where we are.
[SNORTS]
This way.
[GRUNTS]
Who put that tree there?
Daddy Pig has walked
into a tree.
Are you okay,
Daddy Pig?
Yes, I'm fine.
[SNORTS]
This way.
Daddy Pig, do you know
where you're going?
Yes, of course I do.
[SNORTS]
I don't think we'll ever find
our house again.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
I'm sure we will, Peppa.
We're only in our garden.
[QUACKING]
Oh, it's the ducks.
[QUACKS]
Hello, Mrs. Duck.
Have you lost your pond?
[QUACKS]
We're lost too.
We are not lost.
I know exactly where we are.
[SNORTS]
See you later, ducks.
Good luck finding your pond.
Whoa!
[LOUD SPLASH]
ALL:
Oh!
Daddy Pig has found
the duck pond.
[SNORTS]
That's lucky.
Yes. What a stroke of luck.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[QUACKS]
Daddy,
Mrs. Duck says thank you.
You're most welcome,
Mrs. Duck.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[QUACKING]
Now, let's find our house.
[SNORTS]
I'm sure it's this way.
MOMMY RABBIT:
Hello?
Did you hear something?
Yes, I thought
I heard someone say...
Hello?
It's Mommy Rabbit
with Rebecca and Richard.
[SQUEAKS]
Hello, Peppa, we're lost.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Rebecca. We're lost too.
We wanted to go
to the playground.
So did we, but it's too foggy
to get there.
Come on, everyone.
Back to our house
until the fog clears.
Daddy Pig, do you know
where you're going?
Yes, of course I do.
[SNORTS]
This way.
ALL:
Yes, Daddy Pig!
[♪♪]
Ah-ha!
[SNORTS]
I've found our little hill.
We'll soon be home.
ALL:
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
Our house should be
just about here.
Oh!
Daddy Pig has found
a ladder.
[SNORTS]
That's strange,
we don't have a ladder
in our garden.
Goodness me.
Can you see where we are,
Daddy Pig?
Yes, I can.
[LAUGHS]
Daddy, where are we?
Why don't you have a look.
Okay.
Wow!
I can see everything again.
The fog is going away.
[PEPPA GIGGLES]
We're at the playground.
BOTH:
Hooray!
Whee!
We're at the playground.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Seesaw.
Daddy, Mommy!
[LAUGHS]
We're at the playground.
Well, that's lucky.
But I thought
we were trying to get home.
So did I.
Maybe we did get a bit lost
after all.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
It is a rainy day,
and the school roof
has a hole in it.
Children.
We are going to have
a jumble sale.
The money we raise
will pay for a new school roof.
ALL:
Hooray!
Everyone has to bring something
for the jumble sale.
[SNORTS]
What should we bring?
You can bring an old toy
or something
you don't use anymore.
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
The parents have arrived
to pick up the children.
Home time.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Don't forget your old toys
for the jumble sale
tomorrow.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Peppa is choosing a toy
for the jumble sale.
Peppa, have you decided?
Um...
You only have to choose
one toy.
Yes, and it will help pay
for a new school roof.
Okay.
I'm going to give...
Mr. Dinosaur.
[CRYING]
Mr. Dinosaur is George's
favorite toy.
Peppa, you can't give away
Mr. Dinosaur.
Can't I?
No.
Oh, bother.
Sorry, George.
[GIGGLING]
Dinosaur.
[SNORTS]
Why don't you give
your old jack-in-a-box.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Okay.
[SNORTS]
Now, it's your turn, Daddy.
What?
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
We must all give something
to the jumble sale.
[SNORTS]
I'm giving this hat,
and George
is giving this ball.
[SNORTING]
So, what shall Daddy give?
[SNORTS]
I know. The television.
Not the telly!
No, it's too useful.
Um...
I know.
Daddy's smelly slippers.
[SNIFFS AND COUGHS]
No, too smelly.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
I know. Daddy's old chair.
[SPRINGS CREAKING]
But that's an antique.
What does "antique" mean?
Antique means it's very old
and valuable.
But you found it
on a rubbish tip, Daddy Pig.
It's worthless.
It'll be worth a lot of money
when I mend it.
You've been saying that
for ages, Daddy Pig.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
I know.
I'll give these lovely socks
that Granny Pig made me.
PEPPA: Good.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[SNORTING]
I've come to collect
your things
for the jumble sale.
Here they are.
Thank you.
[CREAKING]
And would you like
this old chair?
Oh, most generous.
Goodbye.
ALL: Bye.
Mommy, you gave away
Daddy's chair.
Shh. Don't tell him.
He'll never notice.
[GIGGLES]
It is the day
of the jumble sale.
Hello.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Peppa, how about
this chair?
It's a bit rubbish,
but you can chop it up
and use it for firewood.
But it's an antique.
Is it?
Daddy said it's worth
lots of money.
Well, I never.
I'd better put the price up.
Bye.
[GIGGLING]
Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Hello, Peppa.
What did you give, Suzy?
I gave my nurse's outfit.
I gave my parrot balloon.
I gave my toy monkey.
[MIMICS MONKEY]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SIGH]
I will miss my jack-in-a-box.
Can I buy this jack-in-a-box,
please?
And I'd like
this nurse's outfit.
The parrot balloon, please.
[ALL GIGGLING]
Mommy, Mommy,
look what we've bought.
All your old toys.
We missed them.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Look what I've bought.
It's an antique chair.
Oh, Daddy Pig.
That's not an antique chair.
It is.
Miss Rabbit just said so.
And it matches
my old one.
Yes, Daddy,
that's because...
Shh, Peppa.
...it is your old chair.
What?
But Miss Rabbit
has just charged me
lots of money for it.
Fantastic news,
everybody.
We have just raised
all the money we need
for a new school roof.
ALL:
Hooray!
Thank you,
Daddy Pig.
[LAUGHS]
You're most welcome.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are at the swimming pool.
Daddy Pig is wearing
his swimming costume.
Mommy Pig is wearing
her swimming costume.
Peppa is wearing
Hurry up, George.
Everyone's waiting.
George is wearing
his swimming costume.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Peppa, George,
let Daddy
put on your armbands.
[INHALING THEN BLOWING]
There, George.
Your armbands
make you look very grown-up.
[SNORTS]
Now me.
[INHALING THEN BLOWING]
[GIGGLES]
Good. Now we can go
in the water.
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING]
[CRYING]
It is George's first time
at the swimming pool.
Why don't you put
just one foot in to the water?
[CRIES]
Maybe you should try
the other foot.
[CRYING]
Maybe George should try
both feet at the same time.
[SNORTS]
Good idea.
[SPLASHES]
[GIGGLING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Well done, George.
But you don't need to splash
quite so much.
[GIGGLES]
Here is Rebecca Rabbit
with her little brother,
Richard Rabbit.
[SNORTS] Hello, Rebecca.
[SNORTS]
[SQUEAKS]
Hello, everyone.
[SQUEAKING]
Richard,
hold on to this float
and you can practice
kicking your legs.
[SQUEAKS]
[SNORTS]
George, would you like to try
kicking your legs?
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING AND SPLASHING]
[LAUGHS]
Very good,
but try not to splash.
[SNORTS]
Big children don't splash.
We're very good at swimming.
When George
and Richard are older,
they'll be able to swim like us.
Won't they, Rebecca?
Yes.
[BOTH PANTING]
Oh.
Richard has a toy
watering can.
[SNORTS]
Stop it, Richard.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Oh, dear. Richard has dropped
his watering can into the pool.
[SOBS]
[BOTH CRYING]
Mommy!
Sorry, Richard,
I can't reach.
It's too far down.
Mommy.
I can't swim underwater.
Even I can't swim
underwater.
Hmm.
Please, hold my glasses,
Mommy Pig.
[INHALES]
[GASPING]
ALL: Hooray!
[LAUGHS]
There you go.
[SQUEAKING]
Well done, Daddy Pig.
I am rather good
at swimming underwater.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Huh?
[ALL GIGGLING]
The watering can
is for babies.
[SNORTS]
Can we jump off
the diving boards now?
Sorry, Peppa.
Diving boards are only
for grown-ups.
Oh?
Oh.
Cheer up, you two.
You can watch me dive.
Silly Daddy.
Your tummy is too big.
[LAUGHS]
Nonsense.
I won trophies for my diving
when I was younger.
That was quite a long time ago,
Daddy Pig.
It's lucky I've kept myself
so fit and strong.
Please, hold my glasses,
Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
You'll get a better view
if you watch me
from the side.
Please don't splash us
with water, Daddy.
Of course I won't splash you,
Peppa.
I think I need
a higher board.
Please be careful,
Daddy Pig.
Yes, don't splash us, Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
Don't worry, Peppa.
Don't splash us with water,
Daddy.
I told you
I wouldn't splash.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Clever, Daddy.
Well done, Daddy Pig.
No need for my towel.
I've got a special way
of drying myself.
[ALL EXCLAIM]
Daddy Pig has splashed everyone
with water.
Daddy Pig!
Sorry, everyone.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
[SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]
[SNORTING]